We will fly all over the world
All over the sky
All over time
We will fly to other planets
We've found the secret
We will fly
All over the sky
What a surprise
It's beautiful
On our right you can see the North Pole
And with a little luck the Aurora Borealis
Huh? The Aurora what?
The Northern Lights Michael
And on our left use my workshop
Careful now here we go
Watch out
Oh my god
No problem
Home sweet home
You seen it and on my first try too
Um yeah
Great job
Hey look
Shall I give you a tour?
Yeah
I don't like this it's too dark in here
Shut it
It worked
Wow Santa's workshop
Dang it
Steve hurt
Oh we're gonna miss a tour
My gift machine
Ho ho ho ho
Come on sweet put your pocket to it
I'm taking quick falling on my hand
Yeah well I'd like to see you try it
I am trying you fool
Help these impersonals mister sweet
I'm gonna take a look at our way
Right away Captain
Well impressive huh?
It's completely extra astonishing
How does it work?
I don't have the slightest idea
That's why I have Murphy
He handles everything technical around here
Hello kids
Hello everybody
Your machine is so great mister Murphy
Why thank you young man
Would you like to know how it works?
Absolutely
Excellent
So this is the beginning of the production line
Wow now no touching
I hate fingerprints
Murphy
I'm touching it makes it all dirty
Now Murphy be nice
Here's where we put the letters I have received and approved
Does that mean?
Yes Michael
I love your dinosaur drawing
Yes
Next the machine analyzes the letter
Deciphes the spine we scrawn
And corrects belly mistakes
Murphy
They're here to have fun
Yeah yeah okay I'm sorry
And then it makes the present
Oh
Wow
This machine can make anything
And I mean anything
Did you hear that's me?
A machine that makes everything I want
Like for example
A giant giant tit-trouser
I thought I'd never make
Look that's wonderful
Hey Wendy can you lend me a pen?
Oh no Michael
That would throw the wish a man out of order
This is the most important part of the machine
The part that makes the wishes come true
But it can never be used for selfish purposes
So that means you can never make presents for yourself Santa?
I don't know of a better gift than making a child happy
Let's continue shall we?
If you don't mind
I still have a few things to fix before the big night tonight
Of course Murphy
And thank you
Thank you Mr. S
Wow
We're gonna learn how to be Santa's house
Awesome
There's no ag about it
Here my dear Dagen
Play this to the end of your rope
Okay Captain
Right up!
Huh ?
Uh...
You're up, Dagen
Wow
And here's the gift wrapping machine
place the toys in here.
And the presents come out of here.
Another invention by my dear Muffin.
This is outrageous! This is scandalous!
I will report this to Santa Claus!
Of course! Of course! But until then, you're going to explain to me how your marvelous machine works!
Never!
Chilu, do you think we can find a way to loosen this gentleman's tongue?
You think you can scare me? I know, Kung Fu!
I mean, I read a book about Kung Fu. I know how to defend myself!
I shall hum it in fighting!
Chilu!
Tickle tickle tickle!
Okay! Okay! I'll talk! I'll talk!
I'm all ears!
You're so funny!
Michael, it might be fragile. She calmed down. I was just looking.
Is that normal?
I don't think so. Muffin! Muffin!
That's stupid! Who would ever ask for money at Christmas?
I think I have an idea.
Captain? It's an honor to sue under your tyrannical yolk.
The pirates! I knew it!
Stop! If you use the machine for selfish means, you'll break it!
For the time being, it looks like it's working just perfectly.
It's a far treasure!
There's something for everyone! Today is Christmas for pirates!
I got one! I got...!
One! I... I...
You're gonna pay for this UP, Pray Pirate!
Perfect timing! I have plenty of money!
Good one, Cap!
Oh no!
The wolves! Try to stop them from popping out!
Oh! Holy! Oh! That one's going to blow!
Got it!
That wasn't so bad! No reason to panic like that's me!
Too now! Not so bad! The machine is broken!
Because of you, there won't be any Christmas presents this year!
Good! Humbug! I hate Christmas anyway!
So I wish you a very miserable Christmas!
Santa Claus, how do we fix this machine?
What?
Er... well...
Hooray!
Okay, friends, we don't have much time to save Christmas, so here's what we're going to do.
Elves, give these kids tools! Kids, would you please help the elves tighten all the nuts and bolts?
Santa, I need you to give Murph in a hand!
Er... Murphin? Er... Murphin? I can't believe it! Where did it get to?
Murph in! Is he a little Elfall in green?
The one with the cane we left out on the roof?
The wish about is broken? Oh boy, oh boy, oh boy! What are we going to do?
I was kind of hoping you would tell us, Murphin?
Well, I suppose we need to go to Neverland to get here.
Perfect! Let's go! Hurry! You can explain on the way!
There's no way I'm getting in the stay of his driving! It's too scary!
Oh, nothing! I've improved over time, you know, but I do believe John would love to drive the sled.
You know it! Well... Okay, but don't fly too fast! I promise!
Whoa! Awesome, John! Ready to land?
Oh, we alive!
Yeah!
Not bad, young man, not bad!
Pretty little fairy! Could you go find your godmothers?
The flower ladies?
Yes! We need their magic!
Okay, Murph and... right away!
Hmm... These plans are super complicated.
Oh, complicated indeed!
Katie, hand me the 29 backhand fender, please.
Does that even exist?
Just give him the bright green one there.
The thing with string bean is to act like you totally understand him.
There you go!
This is my dear digging! After all I've done for you!
You never listen! All you wanted to do is steal Christmas!
The result? We just have a few gold coins and we won't even get any presents!
We need to find a way to escape!
I'm working on a cap!
I'm working on it!
Hello, my friends!
Hello, Murphon!
If it's no bother...
No bother!
What did you think, Peter? I was a being polite, that's all!
But being polite isn't something you young people know anything about anymore!
Yes, well, so ladies, in order to repair the Wishamat, I will need four pieces of the never tree!
One for each season!
Understood.
Why, of course!
The Wishamat makes dreams come true and dreams begin in the imagination!
Like this tree! That's so clever!
Easy day!
Gee-doo's coming back!
Super!
Why is he?
Aren't you supposed to be tied up?
Not bad, Mr. Smee! Not bad!
Thank you, kid!
The pirates! They broke a smee!
Indeed! And we're ready to celebrate!
We're back!
Lossamine for spring...
Yeah...
Ripping in for summer...
Transformation for autumn...
Hibernation for winter...
This is the cycle of the seasons that we honor!
Thank you, ladies!
Come on, kids! We have to hurry! The machine still isn't repaired!
Let's go!
Toodles!
Uh, Iris...
Oh!
Toodles!
I've been hit
They're just self-adhesive, you dummy!
Tell me immediately how we go!
To the neverland!
But, captain, the children left with my sleigh!
You have to face the backslash!
You're stuck here!
I don't want to stay here! It's too cold!
Yeah!
Matter of fact!
They're not broken!
You blame Santa Claus alone!
You mean the king of the stupidest holiday of the year?
I have a great idea! I'll be right back!
Huh?
To the rescue!
Who?
No!
Gotcha!
Yeehaw!
Your goose is cut, you'll be there.
Oh!
This is... this is Santa Claus!
I didn't want to ruin your day.
I am...
How'd Percy?
Oh, merry Christmas!
What?
But he hasn't exactly been nice.
Go ahead, Captain.
Open it.
Oh!
It's...!
The Model X74AB hook, with the latest multi-tool option.
Exactly what you hope for, right?
Santa Claus?
He nearly ruined Christmas.
And he's a bad guy, isn't he?
Bad guys don't get presents, do they?
Christmas is also a time of forgiveness and he needed to learn to love Christmas again.
I do believe it's worth...
Well, guess I'll have to trust you on that one.
I have a present.
I have a...
What?
Aren't you happy?
I got a present after all?
Well, that's quite nice, Captain.
But the machine is broken, so the rest of us won't be getting any presents.
You're going to spoil my pleasure.
What did you wait for you, Mr. Lizzy Bones?
Go help the kids fix it.
You can see for a while that they're lost.
Get to it.
Did you hear your captain?
Everyone, get to work.
Did you bring back what you need to fix the whistle mat?
Four pieces of the never tree to make dreams come true.
Hey, hello.
They're fragile.
Kids today.
Okay.
We're split into groups.
Pirates come with me.
Kids go and send here.
Merry Christmas, Captain.
Merry Christmas, Bacon.
Wow.
Any progress?
Does it work?
Captain, let him work in peace.
Yeah, well, you're bothering him too.
No, I'm not.
And anyway, we wouldn't be here if you hadn't tried to steal Christmas, so...
It's fixed!
What do you mean, steal Christmas?
I just wanted treasure.
What?
You're nothing but a rotten thief, you old sea cucumber.
What's more, you broke all the machines.
So because of you, there'll be no presents for anyone this year.
Of course there will be.
Everything I'll be faced in thanks to who they, your little rat, thanks to us pirates.
Hey, Santa.
Don't you think it's mission something?
Yeah, right.
It's all thanks to you.
Oh, yeah.
That's true.
That should come from them.
You're right, Peter.
This is all my fault.
For once, we agree on something.
But if we all pitch in, if all of us make their presents by hand,
we might be able to do it.
But we'll have to be allies.
Just for tonight.
What do you say yet, Dirty Roskel?
I say okay.
You'll pair it.
It works.
It works!
Yes, indeed.
What was missing to make the whole thing work was a little Christmas spirit.
And what could be better than a nice truce to save the most beautiful holiday of all?
Ha!
Here's the present for George and Mary.
Thanks.
Here you go.
I'm ready, I'm ready, I'm ready.
This has been the most beautiful Christmas of my life.
Me too.
Excuse me?
Whoo!